Finding Aid to the San Francisco Department of Public Health AIDS Office records SFH 4
San Francisco History Center, San Francisco Public Library
- Contracts and Related Documents, 1984-1993; Record Group 2; 39 Cubic Feet
  - Contract Development Files, Series 16
    - ERIC (CPC) Contract Development, Subseries 16.6
      - Bay View Hunters Point Foundation: General Funds Workpapers (Box 52, Folder 22)
        - Contract, Workpapers, Draft (Box 52, Folder 24)
        - STATE I&E Workpapers (Box 52, Folder 25)
        - STATE I&E Correspondence (Box 52, Folder 26)
      - Catholic Charities: STATE RAS Correspondence (Box 52, Folder 27)
      - 18th Street Services: STATE I&E Workpapers (Box 52, Folder 28)
      - Friendship House: CDC Correspondence (Box 52, Folder 31-32)
        - CDC Workpapers (Box 52, Folder 33)
        - STATE I&E Workpapers (Box 52, Folder 34)
        - STATE I&E Correspondence (Box 52, Folder 35)
        - loose Contracts & papers (Box 52, Folder 36-37)
      - Instituto (F/R): Block/CDC Correspondence (Box 52, Folder 38-39)
        - Workpapers (Box 52, Folder 40)
        - Notes (Box 52, Folder 41)
        - STATE I&E Correspondence (Box 52, Folder 42)
        - STATE I&E Workpapers (Box 52, Folder 43)
      - Bidding Exemption Requests, 87/88, 1987-1988 (Box 52, Folder 44)
      - AIDS Health Project MHAV: Correspondence (Box 52, Folder 45-46)
      - Asian American Recovery Services: Asian/PI Survey Project 254 (Box 52, Folder 47-48)
      - Mission Neighborhood Health Center: APFUC (Box 52, Folder 49-50)
      - Pacific Presbyterian Medical Center /Visiting Nurses Hospice: General Funds / HRSA (Box 52, Folder 51)
      - Pacific Presbyterian Medical Center: CT83-94007 7-1-89 - 9-30-89, July 1, 1989 - September 30, 1989 (Box 52, Folder 52)
    - POC Agencies Contract Development Files, Subseries 16.7
      - Monitoring Reports Gen Fund 91-92 (Box 53, Folder 1)
      - Home CARE Com Skills Training Correspondence (Formula) (Box 53, Folder 2)
        - Contract (Box 53, Folder 3)
      - Instituto Familiar de la Raza CARE Correspondence (Box 53, Folder 4)
        - Contract Corresp (Formula) (Box 53, Folder 5)
        - Contract 91-92 (Formula) (Box 53, Folder 6)
      - Bridge For Kids Correspondence (Formula) (Box 53, Folder 7)
        - Contract (Box 53, Folder 8)
      - American Indian AIDS Institute. Case Management: Contract (Box 53, Folder 9)
        - CM/Practical Support Correspondence (Box 53, Folder 10)
      - SFAF: Social Services Correspondence (Box 53, Folder 11)
        - Contract (Box 53, Folder 12)
        - Monitoring Report GF 91-92 (Box 53, Folder 13)
      - Shanti Practical Support Correspondence (Box 53, Folder 14)
        - Contract Development GF (Box 53, Folder 15)
        - Crossings Program Contract (Supplemental) (Box 53, Folder 16)
        - Contract (Formula) (Box 53, Folder 17)
        - (Practical Support/LNA) (Box 53, Folder 18)
      - Tenderloin AIDS Network Contract 91-92 (Formula) (Box 53, Folder 19)
        - Correspondence (Formula) (Box 53, Folder 20)
      - Progress Report (Box 53, Folder 21)
      - I & E Progress Report (Box 53, Folder 22)
      - Scope of Work, 88/89 (Box 53, Folder 23)
      - State Education/Prevention, 88/89 (Box 53, Folder 24)
      - RFP #051 (Box 53, Folder 25)
      - RFP #052 (Box 53, Folder 26)
      - #010-017 Bidders Conference Minutes (Box 53, Folder 27)
      - 89 RFP Filipino Sr (Box 53, Folder 28)
      - RFP #052: AIDS Education....SF's Asian, Black & Latino Community -loose report (Box 53, Folder 29)
      - RFP Outreach/Onsite Education 86-7 CDC/HERR (Box 53, Folder 30)
      - Minority Initiative RFP (Box 53, Folder 31-32)
      - Monitoring Reports (Box 53, Folder 33-34)
      - Monitoring Correspondence (Box 53, Folder 35)
      - MNHC Monitoring (Box 53, Folder 36)
      - Shanti Project / Home Care Training / Monitoring Reports (Box 53, Folder 37)
      - RFP Practical Support (Box 53, Folder 38)
      - National Task Force on AIDS Prevention (NTFAP) Early Intervention Advocacy General Fund (Box 53, Folder 39)
      - NTFAP Early Intervention General Fund Quarterly Reports (Box 53, Folder 40)
      - NTFAP Early Intervention General Fund Correspondence (Box 53, Folder 41)
      - NTFAP Community Events Ind Treatment Adv. General Fund Monitoring Report (Box 53, Folder 42)
      - NTFAP Early Intervention General Fund Contract Prep Materials (Box 53, Folder 43)
      - GF Monitoring (Box 53, Folder 44)
      - GMOC / EACH Comm. Events Ind. Treatment Adv. CARE 1 Monitoring Report (Box 53, Folder 45)
      - NTFAP Federal Care Title 1 Correspondence (Box 53, Folder 46)
      - NTFAP Federal Care Title 1. Units of Service Modif. (Box 53, Folder 47)
      - NTFAP Federal Care Title 1. Quarterly Rep (Box 53, Folder 48)
      - SFAF Contract (Box 53, Folder 49)
      - SFAF Multicultural Services GF Monitoring Information (Box 53, Folder 50)
      - BAHSES - BWMT / MACT Contract (Box 53, Folder 51)
      - BAHSES - Monitoring Report Responses (Box 53, Folder 52)
      - BAHSES Correspondence (Box 53, Folder 53)
    - EIRC (CPC) Development Files & Reports, Subseries 16.8
      - UCSF/AIDS Health Project: EIRC Linkage/Support (Box 54, Folder 1)
        - Contract Notes (Box 54, Folder 2)
        - Quarterly Reports (Box 54, Folder 3)
        - Correspondence (Box 54, Folder 4)
        - Budget Mods. (Box 54, Folder 5)
        - Units of Servicess Mods (Box 54, Folder 6)
        - Fiscal/UOS Analysis (Box 54, Folder 7)
      - UCSF/AIDS Health Project EIRC Administration (Box 54, Folder 8)
        - Contract Notes (Box 54, Folder 9)
        - Correspondence (Box 54, Folder 10)
        - Quarterly Reports (Box 54, Folder 11-12)
        - Monitoring Reports (Box 54, Folder 13)
      - UCSF/AIDS Health Project: EIRC Central Intake GF (Box 54, Folder 14)
        - Contract Notes (Box 54, Folder 15)
        - Quarterly Reports (Box 54, Folder 16)
        - Monitoring Reports (Box 54, Folder 17)
        - Correspondence (Box 54, Folder 18)
        - Compendium (Box 54, Folder 19)
        - Budget Models (Box 54, Folder 20)
        - Units of Service (Box 54, Folder 21)
        - Fiscal / UOS Analysis (Box 54, Folder 22)
      - EIRC Site Administration Continued (Box 54, Folder 23-26)
      - AHP / NTFAP / CAL-PEP Site Admin. Contract Mod. (Box 54, Folder 27)
      - UCSF - CPC Site Admin. Modif, 4/92 (Box 54, Folder 28)
      - AHP / CAL-PEP Budget Mod., January 1993 (Box 54, Folder 29)
      - Operation Concern Psych Support Services CARE 7/90-7/91 (Box 54, Folder 30)
      - 18th Street Services Linkage (EIRC) G F 10/91 - 6/92 (Box 55, Folder 1)
        - Contract Notes (Box 55, Folder 2)
        - Correspondence (Box 55, Folder 3)
        - Budget Mods. (Box 55, Folder 4)
        - Monitoring Reports (Box 55, Folder 5)
        - Quart. Reports (Box 55, Folder 6)
        - Units of Service Mods (Box 55, Folder 7)
        - Fiscal / UOS Analysis (Box 55, Folder 8)
      - CURAS: Linkage, Education & Support GF, September 1991- June 1992 (Box 55, Folder 9)
        - Contract Notes (Box 55, Folder 10)
        - Correspondence (Box 55, Folder 11)
        - Quart. Reports (Box 55, Folder 12)
        - Budget Mods. (Box 55, Folder 13)
        - Monitoring Reports (Box 55, Folder 14)
        - Crisis (Box 55, Folder 15)
        - Fiscal / UOS Analysis (Box 55, Folder 16)
        - Units of Service Mods (Box 55, Folder 17)
        - CURAS: Supplemental Contract (Box 55, Folder 18)
      - CURAS: CARE II, November 1991-May 1992 (Box 55, Folder 19)
      - GCHP & FTFA: Case Management CARE II, October 1991-May 1992 (Box 55, Folder 20)
      - CURAS: Client Advocacy CARE l Monitoring Report (Box 55, Folder 21)
      - GCPH & FTFA: Case management: CARE II (Box 55, Folder 22)
        - Contract Notes (Box 55, Folder 23)
        - Quart. Reports (Box 55, Folder 24)
        - Correspondence (Box 55, Folder 25)
        - Budget Mods. (Box 55, Folder 26)
      - GCHP / FTFA Educa/Linkage (EIRC) GF, September 1991-June 1992 (Box 55, Folder 27)
        - Quart. Reports (Box 55, Folder 28)
        - Contract Notes (Box 55, Folder 29)
        - Correspondence (Box 55, Folder 30)
      - GCHP / FTFA Client Advocacy: CARE I/Suppl, July 1991-June 1992 (Box 55, Folder 31)
        - Quarterly Reports (Box 55, Folder 32)
        - Budget Mods. (Box 55, Folder 33)
        - Monitoring Report (Box 55, Folder 34)
      - Asian American Health Forum Care: Monitoring, November 1991 (Box 55, Folder 35)
      - GCHP / FTFA: Educ/Linkage (EIRC) GF Monitoring Report (Box 55, Folder 36)
      - Glide Foundation: Psychosoc Sup (EIRC), September 1991-June 1992 (Box 55, Folder 37)
      - Bay View Hunters Point Foundation CT83-94009 (Box 55, Folder 42)
      - BVHPF CT83-94019 (Box 55, Folder 43)
      - BVHPF CT83-94082 (Box 55, Folder 44)
      - BVHPF CT83-94082 modification (Box 55, Folder 45)
    - First Contract Development Files, Monitoring Reports, 1984-1991; Subseries 16.9
      - San Francisco AIDS Foundation
        - 1984-1985 (Box 56, Folder 1)
        - Proj 253 86-87 (Box 56, Folder 2)
        - Bureau Disease Control 7/86-6/87 (Box 56, Folder 3)
        - Social Service Ad Valorem 7/86-6/87 (Box 56, Folder 4)
        - Education Project 252 87-87 (Box 56, Folder 5)
      - IFR (Box 56, Folder 6)
      - LAP Invoices, 1988 (Box 56, Folder 7)
      - AARS Contracts (Box 56, Folder 8)
      - San Francisco AIDS Foundation
        - Correspondence (Box 56, Folder 9)
        - Reports (Box 56, Folder 10)
        - Request for Proposal (Box 56, Folder 11)
      - AHP
        - Invoices (Box 56, Folder 12)
        - Reports (Box 56, Folder 13)
        - Request for Proposal (Box 56, Folder 14)
      - SFAF Contract CT83-00265 A (Box 56, Folder 15)
      - Indian AIDS Project (Box 56, Folder 16)
      - Civil Grand Jury (AIDS) 87-89 (Box 56, Folder 17)
      - PPMC
        - VN & H Contract Order CT83-07051 (Box 56, Folder 18)
        - 7/90-6-91 (State) (Box 56, Folder 19)
      - CMMC / VNH Quarterly Report 90-91 (Box 56, Folder 20)
      - PPMC / VNH Monitoring Report 90-91 (Box 56, Folder 21)
      - SFAF
        - Correspondence 90-91 (Box 56, Folder 22)
        - Quarterly Report 90-91 (Box 56, Folder 23)
        - Monitoring Report 90-91 (Box 56, Folder 24)
      - St. Mary's Hospital
        - Contract 90-91 (Box 56, Folder 25)
        - HIV Services. Correpondence 90-91 (Box 56, Folder 26)
        - HIV Services. Request for Proposal 90-91 (Box 56, Folder 27)
      - Larkin Street Youth Center Quarterly Report 90-91 (Box 56, Folder 28)
      - Mission Neighborhood Health Center. Correspondence 90-91 (Box 56, Folder 29)
      - National Task Force on AIDS
        - Monitoring Report 90-91 (Box 56, Folder 30)
        - Quarterly Report 90-91 (Box 56, Folder 31)
        - Request for Proposal (Box 56, Folder 32)
        - Correspondence 90-91 (Box 56, Folder 33)
    - POC Agencies; Contract Development Files, 1989-1991; Subseries 16.10
      - Marshia Herring Files, 1989-1991
        - ASIAN AIDS PROJECT, 1990-1991 (Box 57, Folder 1)
        - American Indian AIDS Institute: 1989-90 Reports, 1989-1990 (Box 57, Folder 2)
          - Monitoring Materials (Box 57, Folder 3)
          - Correspondence 1989-90 (Box 57, Folder 4)
        - AAP
          - Correspondence 1989-90 (Box 57, Folder 5)
          - Reports 1989-90 (Box 57, Folder 6)
        - Bay View Hunters Point Foundation:, 1990-1991 (Box 57, Folder 7-8)
          - Contracts / Correspondence (Box 57, Folder 9-10)
        - CAL-PEP: 1990-91 Correspondence / RFP #077-90 (Box 57, Folder 11-12)
        - 18th Street Services: Programs, 1990-1991 (Box 57, Folder 13-14)
        - Asian American Health Forum: Billings / Invoices, 1989-1990 (Box 57, Folder 15)
        - Community United in Response to AIDS / SIDA (CURAS), 1990 (Box 57, Folder 16)
        - EIRC (MICHAEL BALA-MISC. FILES / 1988-91) (Box 57, Folder 17-21)
        - Shanti Monitoring 88/89 (Box 57, Folder 22)
    - POC Agencies; Prevention Contract Development Files, Subseries 16.11
      - Prevention Branch - Marshia Herring - STATE - CDC Committees 90/91 (Box 58, Folder 1)
      - STATE Prevention 91/92 (Box 58, Folder 2)
      - STATE Prevention 1989-90 (Box 58, Folder 3)
      - I&E - Reports (Box 58, Folder 4)
      - SFAF 1989-90: Monitoring Protocol (Box 58, Folder 5)
      - O.C.: Contracts (Box 58, Folder 6)
      - Native American & AIDS (Box 58, Folder 7)
      - Tenderloin AIDS Network (Box 58, Folder 8)
      - Third World AIDS Advisory Task Force (Box 58, Folder 9)
      - Women's AID Network (Box 58, Folder 10)
      - Women's Institute for Mental Health / IRIS (Box 58, Folder 11)
      - Black Coalition On AIDS (Box 58, Folder 12)
      - C.O.Y.O.T.E. (Box 58, Folder 13)
      - CURAS (Box 58, Folder 14)
      - 18th Street Services (Box 58, Folder 15)
      - Gay Pacific Alliance (Box 58, Folder 16)
      - Mission Neighborhood Health Center (Box 58, Folder 17)
      - Education (Box 58, Folder 18)
      - Native Americans (Box 58, Folder 19)
      - AlAISF (Box 58, Folder 20)
      - Asian AIDS Task Force (Box 58, Folder 21)
      - Asian American Residential Recovery Services (Box 58, Folder 22)
      - BVHP (Box 58, Folder 23)
      - American Indians, Inc "Proposal" (Box 58, Folder 24)
      - AlAISF: Contracts, 1988-1989 (Box 58, Folder 25)
      - AARRS / AAP "Proposal", 1987-1988 (Box 58, Folder 26)
      - BVHP: Contracts / Proposal, 1988-1989 (Box 58, Folder 27-29)
      - 18th Street Services: Contracts, 1988-1989 (Box 58, Folder 30)
      - IF / R: Contracts (Box 58, Folder 31)
      - RFP #046-89: Instituto Familiar loose report (Box 58, Folder 32)
      - RFP #057-90: Gay / Bisexual Male Relapse (Box 58, Folder 33)
      - RFP #055-90: Correspondence (Box 58, Folder 34)
      - RFP #055-90: RFP Newsletter (Box 58, Folder 35)
      - RFP #055-90: Review & Selection (Box 58, Folder 36)
      - RFP #055-90: Misc. papers/reports HIV and Newsletter (Box 58, Folder 37)
    - POC Agencies; Prevention Contract Development & Monitoring Reports, Subseries 16.12
      - American Indian AIDS Institute.: CDC Correspondence (Box 59, Folder 1)
      - Asian American Recovery Services:
        - CDC / Asian Survey Workpapers (Box 59, Folder 2)
        - CDC / Asian Survey Correspondence (Box 59, Folder 3)
        - CDC / HRSA Workpapers (Box 59, Folder 4)
        - CDC / HRSA Correspondence (Box 59, Folder 5)
        - CDC / HRSA Modified Proposal (Box 59, Folder 6)
        - CDC (Education) Correspondence (Box 59, Folder 7)
        - CDC (Educ) Workpapers (Box 59, Folder 8)
        - GenFunds Correspondence (Box 59, Folder 9)
        - GenFunds Workpapers (Box 59, Folder 10)
        - GenFunds Program Review (Box 59, Folder 11)
      - Bay View Hunters Point Fountation:
        - CDC/NIDA Correspondence (Box 59, Folder 12)
        - CDC/NIDA Workpapers (Box 59, Folder 13)
        - CDC/NIDA Notes (Box 59, Folder 14)
      - San Francisco AIDS Foundation Monitoring Reports 87/88 (Box 59, Folder 15)
      - AHP/ASAP Monitoring Reports (Box 59, Folder 16)
      - AHP Contract Monitoring (Box 59, Folder 17)
      - AIDS Health Project MH-AV Monitoring Reports (Box 59, Folder 18)
      - Youth Projects Inc Program Reports 87/88 (Box 59, Folder 19)
      - Extended Hospital Care Program Reports (Box 59, Folder 20)
      - Asian American Recovery Services
      - AIDS Health Proj Minority ATS Monitoring Reports (Box 59, Folder 24)
      - AIDS Health Project ATS Monitoring Reports (Box 59, Folder 25)
      - BVHP-MAPA Ad valorem Monitoring Reports (Box 59, Folder 26)
      - BVHP-MAPA State I&E Monitoring Reports (Box 59, Folder 27)
      - Home Health Care STATE Block Grant Monitoring Reports (Box 59, Folder 28)
      - Home Health Care STATE Home Support Monitoring Reports (Box 59, Folder 29)
      - Home Health Care AV Monitoring Reports (Box 59, Folder 30)
      - Friendship House / Am Indians Block Grant Monitoring Reports (Box 59, Folder 31)
      - 18th Street Services STATE I&E Monitoring Reports (Box 59, Folder 32)
      - Instituto Familiar Ad valorem Monitoring Reports (Box 59, Folder 33)
      - Operation Concern Monitoring Reports (Box 59)
      - San Francisco AIDS Foundation
      - Cross-cultural Training for AIDS Services CT83-72048 (Box 59, Folder 39)
      - Epidemologic Study of Natural History of HIV in Homosexual / Bisexual Men (Box 59, Folder 40)
      - Study of Transfusion Associated AIDS UCSF-CHR #H5021-00047-06 (Box 59, Folder 41)
  - Monitoring Reports, Circa 1989-1990; Series 17
    - Alternative Site Computer (Box 62, Folder 1-6)
    - Shanti: Genral Funds: Program Reports (Box 62, Folder 7)
    - Shanti: STATE RAS Program Reports (Box 62, Folder 8)
    - Women's Inst Mental Health State I & E Program Reports (Box 62, Folder 9)
    - Women's Inst Mental Health Monitoring, General (Box 62, Folder 10)
    - AIDS Day Care HRSA Monitoring Reports (Box 62, Folder 11)
    - AIDS Health Project / UC
      - CDC Monitoring Reports (Box 62, Folder 12)
      - GF/Men Hlth Monitoring Reports (Box 62, Folder 13)
      - PHS/HRSA Monitoring Reports (Box 62, Folder 14)
    - American Indian AIDS Institute
      - CDC Monitoring Reports (Box 62, Folder 15)
      - STATE I&E (Box 62, Folder 16)
    - Asian American Recovery Services Monitoring Reports (Box 62, Folder 17)
    - Bay View Hunters Point Foundation
      - CDC / NIDA Monitoring Reports (Box 62, Folder 18)
      - Gen Funds Monitoring Reports (Box 62, Folder 19)
      - STATE I&E Monitoring Reports (Box 62, Folder 20)
    - 18th Street Services: STATE I&E Monitoring Reports (Box 62, Folder 21)
    - Instituto Familiar Block/CDC Monitoring Reports (Box 62, Folder 22)
    - Instituto Familiar STATE I&E Monitoring Reports (Box 62, Folder 23)
    - Operation Concern Gen. Funds Monitoring Reports (Box 62, Folder 24)
    - PPMC/VNH GF/HRSA Monitoring Reports (Box 62, Folder 25)
    - SF Department of Public Health Monitoring Team Review (Box 62, Folder 26)
    - SFAF / Client Services GF Monitoring Reports (Box 62, Folder 27)
    - SFAF / Education GF/Block/CDC Monitoring Reports (Box 62, Folder 28-29)
    - SFAF / Food Bank STATE I&E Monitoring Reports (Box 62, Folder 30)
    - Shanti General Funds Monitoring Reports (Box 62, Folder 31)
    - Women's Institute Monitoring Reports (Box 62, Folder 32)
    - Women's Institute STATE I&E Monitoring Reports (Box 62, Folder 33)
  - Contract Processing Documents, 1988-1989; Series 18
    - Shanti Project
      - Shanti Project FY 89-90: Notes (Box 60, Folder 1)
      - GF/RAS FY 88-89: (Box 60, Folder 2)
      - STATE/RAS FY 88-89: STATE/RAS (Box 60, Folder 3-4)
      - 4/89-6/89 STATE / RAS (Box 60, Folder 5)
      - FY 88-89: STATE / RAS (Box 60, Folder 6)
    - UCSF: CT#83-94070 (Box 60, Folder 7)
    - Women's Institute
      - FY88-89 STATE I & E (Box 60, Folder 8)
      - STATE I & E (Box 60, Folder 9)
    - Asian American Recovery Services
      - CT83-84066 (Box 60, Folder 10-11)
      - CDC Asian KABB (Box 60, Folder 12)
    - Hospice / Home Care(PPMC) CT83-90303 (Box 60, Folder 13)
    - BVHP NIDA Street Outreach IVDU (Box 60, Folder 14)
    - BVHP / -18th ST Services Education, Gay / Bi male IVDU State I & E (Box 60, Folder 15)
    - SFDPH AIDS in SF 87-88; Projected Needs & Costs (88-93) (Box 60, Folder 16)
    - Youth Projects Inc: Contract Proc. Doc. 87-8, Correspondence (Box 60, Folder 17-19)
    - Youth Environment Study: NIDA 87-8 12/87-9/88 Contr. Proc. Doc. (Box 60, Folder 20)
    - SFAF: loose reports & Contracts (Box 60, Folder 21-22)
    - Mission Neighborhood Health MedEval STATE/APFU (binder) (Box 60, Folder 23)
    - NABWMT Contracts, reports, papers (Box 60, Folder 24)
    - Pacific Mental Health Services Operation Co 276 Com Outre Demo Project (Box 60, Folder 25)
    - Asian American Recovery Service
      - PHS/HRSA 87/88 Contract Process. Document. (Box 61, Folder 1)
      - Correspondence (Box 61, Folder 2)
      - CT83-72039 (Box 61, Folder 3)
      - FY88-89 HRSA Contr. Proc. Doc (Box 61, Folder 4)
      - Ad Velorium 87/88 Contr. Proc. D (Box 61, Folder 5)
        - API
          - Survey Proj. 254 Correspondence (Box 61, Folder 6)
          - 87-8 Ad valorem Correspondence (Box 61, Folder 7)
          - CT83-71212 (Box 61, Folder 8)
    - Asian AIDS Project Ad Valorem (Box 61, Folder 9)
    - 87-8 BVHP-MAPA:
      - STATE I&E: Correspondence (Box 61, Folder 10)
      - STATE I&E: Contr. Proc. Doc. (Box 61, Folder 11)
      - STATE I&E: Project 430 (Box 61, Folder 12)
      - Ad valorem Correspondence (Box 61, Folder 13)
      - Ad valorem Contr. Proc. Doc. (Box 61, Folder 14-15)
      - State I & E (Box 61, Folder 16)
      - Ad valorem (Box 61, Folder 17)
      - MAPA 87-8 Ad velorem (Box 61, Folder 18)
    - BVHP NIDA
      - NIDA 12/87-9/88: Contr. Proc. Doc. (Box 61, Folder 19)
      - NIDA 12/87-9/88: Correspondence (Box 61, Folder 20)
    - California Nurses Association
      - Block Grant 87/88 Correspondence (Box 61, Folder 21)
      - Block Grant 87/88 Contr. Proc. Doc. (Box 61, Folder 22)
      - STATE I&E: Correspondence (Box 61, Folder 23)
      - STATE I&E: Contr. Proc. Doc. (Box 61, Folder 24)
      - STATE I&E: Contract (Box 61, Folder 25-27)
    - California Public Health Foundation. Cohort Spec. Lab. Correspondence (Box 61, Folder 28-32)
    - 18th Street Services
      - STATE 1& E: 87/88 Correspondence (Box 61, Folder 33)
      - STATE 1& E: 87/88 Contr. Proc. Doc. (Box 61, Folder 34)
      - Contract Modification State I & E (Box 61, Folder 35)
    - Garden Sullivan. AV 87/88 Exten Care. Correspondence (Box 61, Folder 36)
  - Departmental Correspondence, Memos, Reports and Subject Files, 1989-1992; Series 19
    - Closing Down I Moving the CPC 9/92 (Box 63, Folder 1)
    - Family Link (a CBO) 9/91 (Box 63, Folder 2)
    - "Gay Sanctuary" 7/91 (Box 63, Folder 3)
    - Language Services Advisory Committee 10/91 (Box 63, Folder 4)
    - SF AIDS Office Information (Box 63, Folder 5)
    - "New Needs" Memos (Box 63, Folder 6)
    - "New Priorities for Funding" Memorandum (Box 63, Folder 7)
    - Streamlining Committee (Box 63, Folder 8)
    - Transition Report (Box 63, Folder 9)
    - BVHP
      - Alternative Health Care Contract (Box 63, Folder 10)
      - Correspondence 1992-93 (Box 63, Folder 11)
    - ADP
      - Correspondence 1990-91 (Box 63, Folder 12)
      - Correspondence 1989-90 (Box 63, Folder 13)
      - Pre - 1989 Correspondence (Box 63, Folder 14)
    - Home Care Comp Annual Program Report 1992-93 (Box 63, Folder 15)
    - Instituto (Box 63, Folder 16)
    - TARC Annual Report Review, November 1, 1993 (Box 63, Folder 17)
    - Support Center; CARE II (91/92)Training in Non-Profit Management #83-17043 (Box 64, Folder 1)
    - Shanti: G.F. & State RAS Emotional, Practical Support, Housing, Peer Counseling, Van Serv (Box 64, Folder 2-5)
    - 91/92 Exten G.F. Health Servo Ctrs. ERIC (CPC) (Box 64, Folder 6-14)
    - APICA 1991-92 (Box 64, Folder 15)
    - Urban Health Study Contracts (Box 64, Folder 16)
    - 18th Street Services 90/91 Educational Material, 1989-90 (Box 64, Folder 17)
    - Filipino Task Force On AIDS, 1991 (Box 64, Folder 18-19)
    - HAFMC 1989-90 Contracts (Box 64, Folder 20)
    - SF Black Coalition: Correspondence, 1989-1990 (Box 64, Folder 21)
    - Glide AIDS Project 1989-91, 1989-1991 (Box 64, Folder 22)
    - Operation Concern:
      - Contract (Box 64, Folder 23)
      - Correspondence (Box 64, Folder 24)
      - Monitoring Reports (Box 64, Folder 25)
    - San Francisco AIDS Foundation
      - Monitoring Team Review of SFAF Educ Dept, 88/89 (Box 64, Folder 26)
      - Proposal on Prevention of Relapse (3/90) (Box 64, Folder 27)
      - Proposal on Prevention Education to General Public (RFP 091-90) (Box 64, Folder 28)
      - 091-90 Correspondence (Box 64, Folder 29)